Dear,
is that the warning bell?
No way.
A bell?
Mom...
I love you, Lilith.
Mom!
Lilith, take this.
Dad...
You're a good girl, Lilith. I'm proud of you.
Listen carefully:
I can't come with you, because
I need to stay here and protect you.
I don't want to be alone! I want to stay with you!
You can't do that Lilith. You have to live.
Hey! We've found them!
Run for it, Lilith!
Hurry and get out of here!
Hurry!
We've found the last ones.
Kill them all.
What?!
Dad!
Over here! Hurry and get on!
Leave me behind, Lilith!
I don't want to!
Be a good girl and listen to what your father says.
Live!
You must live, Lilith.
For our family's sake.
Dad!
Lilith,
you must not make the same mistakes your mother did.
As the last of the Strigoli.
Strigoli?
Lilith,
there is a stone monument among the thorned plants that will reveal your destiny.
You must find it,
and with it the inscription on the stone
that links to your heritage.
After that, the decision is yours.
O Holy Knight,
Give birth to the child of blood Romuald.
The child
and the father.
If this be done, the Strigoli will rise again.
hanarenaide hanasanaide
Don't leave and don't let go
sono kodou ga tomaru made
Until this heart stops beating
Uchi nare koe wa wazawai no shirabe
My inner voice keeps repeating
mikan no akumu kurikaeshite iru
A melody of disaster, an incomplete nightmare
kono inga tachikireru nara ba
Should I manage to break this cycle of fate
ochite mo kuyamanai
I would have no regret even if it means my doom
utsuro na hai ni bishu wo mitashitara
When the empty cup fills with the finest wine
A sacrifice will be made at the altar
saidan no ue sasageru wa kumotsu
While I yearn for salvation
kyuusai no yume kogare nagara
The hell fire burns my heart
mune yaku gouka
Come, lay a sweet kiss on me, my life stripped bare
saa mukidashi no sono inochi amaku kuchizukete
The noble sacrifice engraved in my skin
hada ni kizamu toutoi gisei
Love no one else but me
watashi dake aishite
Until the day I stop breathing
iki no taeru toki made
Embrace the the corpse weeping crimson tears.
akai namida nagashi nakigara daite ageru
This accursed fate
norowareta sadame wo
This unerasable stigma
nuguenai rakuin wo
Wash them clean with your blood
anata no chi de araikiyomete
And we'll be reborn
umarekawaru
In the darkness we dance madly between life and death
sei to shi to ga yami ni junkan suru
In this holy night
Yeah, it's Cliff.
Infiltration successful.
It's just as we suspected.
Ritsume Academy.
She's definitely here.
Please act quickly. I repeat:
PAQ.
This is bad. The alarm clock broke once more.
Shin-chan, you're running late again.
My bad. Shall we get going then?
Cammot,
be a good girl and watch the house.
Shimoochiai-outa
General
Hospital
I'll be in your care from now on.
I'm the new urologist, Camilla.
Pleased to meet you.
My Lord,
it's almost time to depart for Kurimia.
My Lord.
Wait for me, Shin-chan!
There's nothing like an early-morning sweat.
Kishimoto.
Kishimoto Lilith.
Lilith?
Sorry. I'm Mizumura Shinta.
Are you perhaps heading to the academy?
Because it looked that way to me.
I came here to meet you.
Huh? What?
Our destinies are entwined.
Her hands are freezing cold.
So tender and delicious.
Huh?
Jeez, Shin-chan, how long are you going to stand there?
Hey!
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
What was that all about?
Shin-chan has been staring at the transfer student all day.
Shinta's a jerk!
But it's not just him.
Both of them have been exchanging glances.
Really, he can't stop looking at her.
When I become a novelist,
Shin-chan won't be able to look at anyone but me!
Huh?
I wonder where Shin-chan went.
I was going to ask him to eat lunch with me.
AYO? I mean, are you okay?
Cliff-sensei.
Sorry.
Thank god you're fine.
Did you get left behind by your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
You are the top student in my Ancient Folklore class.
Love is fine, but don't forget about the report, okay?
Cliff-sensei has only been here for a week,
but he's already settled in.
His Ancient Folklore class is entertaining,
and his choice of words is funny,
but he's still cool,
despite being an older man.
Oh, right! I forgot I was searching for Shin-chan.
Umm... What did you want to talk about?
Is something wrong?
I'm still just a freshman, so I don't know much about this academy yet.
But about this morning...
From now on, both of us are going to have sex.
I want to give birth to your child.
What are you saying, Kishimoto-san?
They're freezing.
I don't know how you do things in your country,
but here people that love each other are the only ones doing that sort of thing.
People that love each other?
Yeah, a child is created from the love of two people.
That's what I heard from my grandfather, at least.
That's why...
Love is such a pain.
Romuald's bloodline...
Stop making excuses and have sex with me!
Wait a minute, Kishimoto-san!
I don't have any experience with that kind of stuff.
I mean...
That's why—Wait... Please wait!
I don't know anymore!
Kishimoto-san, we can't just jump into this.
Sorry!
Chizuru.
Shin-chan, so this is where you were.
You see...
This isn't what you think.
Right?
Useless.
Kishimoto-san!
What was that, Shin-chan?
Like I said, it's not what you think.
Even I don't know what it was.
''A child is created from the love of two people.''
Why does it have to be with him?
Stop doing that.
But even though I'm a wolf, didn't I do a pretty good dog impression?
So what if you're a wolf doing a good dog impression?
Touche.
Don't get so irritated.
You need to cheer up, Lilith.
Why is he like this when our destinies are entwined?
If you act like that, he'll definitely get nervous.
I bet he's a virgin.
What should I do?
You should try being gentle.
Why don't you try smiling?
Smile?
Gentleness. Love.
I don't understand.
I have to hurry and carry out what's been written.
Gentleness...
I don't think you should rush it.
Anyway, you shouldn't underestimate Japan's sunlight.
If you stay in it for too long it could become dangerous.
Romuald's bloodline...
That is all I need...
All right, keep it up!
It's time to work out the chest area!
Watch closely!
One, two. One, two!
Idiot!
He's a complete idiot!
This can't be! This can't be!
But still, I've never seen Shin-chan
look at anyone like that.
Shin-chan!
I was surprised.
Yeah, it was sudden.
It's getting dangerous. We must get that last survivor no matter what.
Yeah, I understand.
That's what I've come here for.
WOD.
We will watch over the descendant.
Shin-chan, you overslept again.
Sorry.
Cammot, I'm leaving now.
Be a good girl and watch the house.
Let's go, Chizuru.
Shinta-kun.
You're walking with me.
Kishimoto-san, why are you here?
That's because our destinies are entwined.
That's a good boy, Shinta-kun.
Be gentle with me.
Okay.
Let's go.
You're in the way.
Chizuru.
Shin-chan!
Press button to cross
Hey, Kishimoto-san!
Wait a minute!
I won't wait. I'm in a hurry.
Be a good boy and listen to what I tell you.
But...
Kishimoto-san?
Kishimoto-san, what's wrong?
Are you feeling all right?
Kishimoto-san!
Hmm... Umm...
What should I do now?
Kishimoto-san?
Dad...
As I thought, she's freezing.
No... Together...
Let's escape together,
Dad.
Kishimoto-san, keep it together.
What's wrong, Lilith? Are you hungry?
That's a problem. Your mother won't be back for a while.
All right, I get it.
Your father will make something for you.
'Kay, good girl?
Dad...
Sorry. You looked like you were in pain,
so I thought that might help.
Is that so?
You suddenly collapsed so I tried to make you feel comfortable.
More importantly, you should eat something.
Hmm... This might be a problem.
There's nothing here.
I was only able to find instant ramen.
Would you like me to buy something else?
That's fine.
Are you sure these will do?
I suppose they will.
Well...
They are kind of...
Did I imagine that?
This should do it.
Just a little longer, Lilith.
Your father is making some delicious stew.
It can't be. It's not possible.
Sorry. This is all I can do.
This is horrible.
Horrible?
Really?
It's usually pretty good.
Too much at one tIme~
Still horrible.
You think so?
It's my favorite.
Is it really that bad?
But It has It's own charm~
Row, row!
Let's go! Work that chest.
Row like you're on your way to your lover's place!
Row, row!
What is it with that girl!
That really pissed me off!
There's no way I'm going to lose!
Shin-chan is mine. I won't give him to anybody else!
It's here! Something godlike has arrived.
Is it really that fun to take photos?
Like this?
How about this?
Can you pose like this?
No problem!
Godlike!
Oh, I forgot.
I'll have to write something about Shinta for today.
Today is hopeless, as well as...
So cute!
Shinta is also hopeless.
So I'll have to protect Shinta.
No problem!
Hey, Lilith.
Isn't the girl that's always by that Romuald guy's side in the way?
Hey, hey, Lilith.
Hey, hey, hey, Lilith, hey, hey.
Lilith, hey, hey, hey, Lilith, hey, hey.
Shut up!
Stop that right now.
What feeling is this?
His hands...
...they were warm.
No.
There is no way he's like that.
I have a mission.
Which must be fulfilled no matter what.
I must give birth to the descendant of the Romuald bloodline.
Then kill both him and Mazumure Shinta and bathe in their blood.
That is my destiny!
Mizumura Shinta
Dailing
The number you have dialed is currently out of the signal area or is turned off.
Shin-chan...
What are you doing?
Sakamoto-san?
How long have you been there?
I don't stand out much.
No, that's not true.
I was just lost in thought, that's all.
Thinking about Mizumira Shinta?
How did—I mean...
He'll be taken away.
Are you fine with that?
No, I'm not!
There is no way I'll let that happen!
Where are you going?
To Shin-chan's place!
Lilith, you shouldn't skip school.
I don't feel like I'm doing my job like this.
That was...
Check this out, she has a nice ass and a good pair of breasts.
There's no way Lilith can beat this.
All right, I'm going to take those breasts down for Lilith's sake.
Shin-chan.
I won't let anyone have Shin-chan.
They sure shake a lot.
What was that voice?
Just as I thought, you do have bigger breasts than Lilith.
What did you say?
What's this?
A virgin? Is this the smell of a virgin?
Who
the hell are you?!
So,
why don't you forget about that guy?
If you do that, we might be able to become closer, right?
What?
What's happening?
What is he doing?
No!
Don't get angry now, Boobie-chan.
Thank you for the taste of a virgin's lips.
I was your first, wasn't I?
Wasn't I?
No!
Mission accomplished.
With this, the girl is no longer in the way.
You should be thankful, Lilith.
What was that?
He kissed me.
And it was my first.
What's this, blood?
Shin-chan.
I'm scared.
Thanks for coming.
She's definitely the girl in the reports.
That's right.
Moroin, the only survivor.
Indeed. The only one that survived.
I'm guessing she's in the dorm right now?
Yeah, it's a place that guys can't enter.
Is the guy of Romual blood here, too?
It's DCV time.
DCV?
Destroy those cursed vampires.
This is bad!
I see it.
Tears of joy.
Cute!
So the time has finally come.
I suppose I'll go take a look.
Please wait, sensei.
Sensei!
Since she's just a little girl, the two of us should be able to handle this, right?
You need to talk a bit more.
Cammot, what should I do?
Things haven't been going well lately.
Chizuru, is that you?
I heard your voice a while ago.
Who were you talking to?
Wha—
Kishimoto-san?
My days just keep on repeating
nandomo kurakaesu my days
An echo that makes my head hurt
atama wo yusaburu zankyou
Ah, these fragile feelings I've been hiding
aa kowaresou da boku no kakushita ura no kanjou
That you will reveal in the future
mirai ni dare ga furerareru no
Come on, just a little bit
sukoshi kurai wa ii jan ka
Nobody understands, nobody knows
dare ni mo wakaranai nobody knows
And yet
soredemo
Your delicate feelings
kimi no sensai na omoi ga
And sharp anxiety
eiri na fuan wa mou
Are starting to pierce through me
boku ni tsukisashite
The feelings we screamed out are so far away
futari no koe sakenda omoi wa zutto tooku
I know we'll manage to overcome fate
unmei mo kitto koerareru darou
So that the reality we painted doesn't smear
irozuita ima nijimanai you ni
Bite those lips and don't let go
sono kuchibiru ni ha wo tatete hanasanai